So Pete, I'm going to talk
element widths for a second.
I've heard that relative widths
are better suited for responsive design.
Why is that?
>> Sure.
Let's take a look at
this website for a second.
It's got a beautiful,
panoramic image that's 1200 pixels wide.
On this laptop screen where
the viewport width is 1280 pixels.
No problem, the image fits just fine.
>> Right.
But now, what happens if you shrink
the browser to a size that's below
the image's native width?
>> Yeah!
If I'm not careful,
instead of shrinking and
re-scaling the image, the image
will keep its original dimensions.
Users will need to stroll left and
right to see the whole image.
>> Oh.
That's ugly and annoying.
>> Yeah.
It's not a good experience.
On the Nexus 7, about a third of
the image is going to get cut off, but
on something like an iPhone 5, the users
going to see less than half the image.
They're going to have to scroll left and
right to see the whole thing.
Since CSS pixels vary so widely across
all these different devices, you
shouldn't count on a specific viewport
width for your content to render well.
Large CSS widths or
even absolute positions can result in
elements that are either too big or
don't fit on the screen at all.
This is why you should use
relative positions instead of
absolute positions such as width 100%.